Welcome to the Handmade Market. I'm your host, Xiao Lin.
Today we have over 50 independent handmade artisans
with us here today.
From pottery to weaving to leather goods—
we have everything you could imagine.
Let's interview a pottery vendor—
his teacups are really popular
among young people.
Hi everyone, I'm A-Ming
from Jingdezhen.
I've been making pottery for 8 years now.
Every piece is hand-thrown
and hand-glazed.
So no two pieces are exactly the same.
That's the charm of handmade—
→ Hurry to booth A12
if you want one.
We've prepared 100 limited gifts.
First come, first served.
As the sky darkens, the market is wrapping up.
Thank you so much for your support.
See you next time!